[Music]
this is all is our
spaceship Rose
uh star sun and the s
and we moving in our
trip all the
time it's like a barion
engine barion
engine
great
starboard and our lovers uh is
uh she became a
Stargate when she born a
child and we keep our journey after life
uh and our
mind is
recorded to
[Music]
the and it's a very interesting uh
theories I find
out and first
uh
uh so call it uh staron out was
a
uh King
Tamar from
Georgia it's about tea and it's a long
story on Old Swan gumless
wardian and you call it shui Su Maran
but it's a
actually the IMI it's a final SE from
the dollar first sign and after is a p
is a from the
Robble and the star joury is in
a uh nebula or
[Music]
rbe and
uh it's a quite
uh complicated uh to
learn this word
digal languages like a physics
like
chemistry
Chia
ruia and
B
our and I do do some machine which will
made from light
water and keep walking on this
Direction with levitation and
uh
teleportation uh of a micro
particles at
first
[Music]
but Planet needs the water it's the most
stuff water and we need to create
this get there
[Music]
so and all this
biner
journey it's like a music where like a
music creates MOA
MOA and
uh my grandfather he was a g
gynecologist and his wife
[Applause]
too I knew she was from
ruia or Russia how you say but
uh uh I find out when
Journey she was from dmark or
[Music]
bangar and they unified
uh
B and he made it
Jon
japon like you say but
dominant finist is a Rob like to say
also like you
see and
uh J and it's
a
heres like
herac very interesting
uh they can't directly send to us uh
text but it show us by huge
uh hysterical
uh uh stories that
U what should
we keep uh to do
or
[Music]
I'm sure uh human G or my own bar
Gan it's a possible if I should live the
on
japon uh on a hi building in Sky ski
scrap that I could uh create
my
seismologic uh
again and I could uh say before a
b that is should going to
happens but
um it's pretty much
[Music]
water running away and
uh I have a too much paid friends
uh they all are paid for just be a
friends
or relatives
or
uh that is love
being and but they need also updates
every 49
year
because it happens
automatically on itun and we
can't change anything we just can love
each other
and United uh
our V shaft
and M BR on
F
and Aurora is the name of this
singer Aurora
accents like
in this old shumaran
[Music]
or it's like U she gives me to remember
and I all my life looking for my tling
[Music]
girl and because we not
Journey alone mostly in our
family but with our Lover now is our fa
or
partner partner you
know but uh yeah is people understood uh
to on low
stages because every my cousin uh bar
cousin are my ex uh favorite too is
from past lives uh because my
grandfather is me and she was my
grandmother
and they was in love and
like uncles and tante
or and
bie and
B
City it's about to do immunity
immunity and I
created but
um I don't know there is too lazy
journalists and too
lazy historians or
scientists I think they just uh
play some great figures
uh and just
uh uh keep some social help uh
and that's it I see
so but barti is a
good it's a card like it's
hard so it will be
never
finished but I had to go now out little
bit
uh thank you on bye